Unterberger, S. Herbert Arbitration and Research Files 5636
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
S. Herbert Unterberger Arbitration and Research Files
1971-1981
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Unterberger, S. Herbert
5636
54.75 cubic feet
54.8 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Correspondence, arbitration and research files, speeches and agreements
3338465
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6047: Archives Information File 6174/004: NYSUT Field Services Department Files
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives 227 Ives Hall Tower Road Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheelref@cornell.edu https://catherwood.library.cornell.edu/kheel/
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 23, 2015
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 25, 2019
Aribtration, Industrial -- United States; Unterberger, S. Herbert, 1913-1979; Commonwealth of Pennsylvania; Air Line Pilots Association; California Public Utilities Commission; Allied Chemical & Dye Corporation; Bell Telephone Company; Bendix Corporation; DeLaval; Delbar; Goodell Rubber; Gould Inc.; Mobil Oil Company; International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. Local 405; Pratt & Whitney Aircraft Company; Radio Corporation of America; Texaco
3338465
- Personal Papers: Correspondence, Personal Documents (Box 1)
  - Correspondence Concerning Jobs, 1935-1937 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Nat. Res. Proj. - Correspondence, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - State of Pennsylvania Civil Service, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Arbitration, 1960-1965 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - U. of P., 1955-1960 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence 1947 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Leather Promotion, 1956-1960 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - GAW Articles, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - CCH - Given Wage, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Wage Stabilization Board, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - American Economic Review, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - National Sand and Gravel Cooperation, 1951-1953 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Civil Service + Government Personnel, 1934-1938 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Articles, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Labor Relation Information Bureau, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Robert E. Griffin, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - S. Herbert Unterberger - Personal, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - S.H.O., 1957-1964 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Misc., 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Herb Unterberger (Bhd. Econ, Theory.), 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - School Reco DJ Reports, etc., 1956 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Personal Papers: Professional Organizations. IncludesNational Academy of Arbitrators, American Arbitration Association, Realty Board. (Box 2)
  - Arbitration - AAA - FMCS, 1948-1949 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - NAA + FMCS, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - National Seat of Arbitration, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Realty Advisory Board, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Misc. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Wage Incentive Speeches, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Report on New York Office Building Survey, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Misc., 1974-1977 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 485 5th Avenue, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 21 Sperry Road 1290, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 50 Rockefeller Plaza, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 200 Park Ave., 1975 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 235 E. 42nd, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 26 Bdway #10, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 113 W. 42nd, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 570 5th Ave., 1975 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - 386 Pr. A. So., 1975 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 1790 Bdway #1, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - 2 Lafayette St. #12, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 15 Park Row #7, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - 12 E. 41 St., 1975 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - 415 Lexington, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - 315 Lexington, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - 274 Madison Ave., 1975 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - 369 Lex, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - 271 Church St., 1975 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - 49 E. 45th, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - 121 E. 60th, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Personal Papers: Publications by Unterberger. Includes National War Labor Board writings, Bureau of Labor Statistics, dissertation, drafts, notes, research files, articles, books. (Box 2A)
  - Collective Bargaining Provisions (Seniority Provisions), 1948 (Box 2A, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Bound
  - U.S. Department of Labor, 1949 (Box 2A, Folder 2)
  - National War Labor Board, 1943 (Box 2A, Folder 3)
  - Wage Brackets, 1945 (Box 2A, Folder 4)
  - National War Labor Board, 1944 (Box 2A, Folder 5)
  - National War Labor Board, 1935-1945 (Box 2A, Folder 6)
- Personal Papers: Publications by Unterberger. Includes National War Labor Board writings, Bureau of Labor Statistics, dissertation, drafts, notes, research files, articles, books. (Box 2B)
  - Wage Stabilization Division - National War Labor Board, 1945 (Box 2B, Folder 1)
  - Works Progress Administration, 1935-1937 (Box 2B, Folder 2)
  - Economic Stabilization Agency Wage Stabilization Board, 1951 (Box 2B, Folder 3)
  - National War Labor Board Wage Report, 1945 (Box 2B, Folder 4)
  - 'Wages', 1950 (Box 2B, Folder 5)
  - H. Unterberger, 1943 (Box 2B, Folder 6)
  - Office of War Information National War Labor Board, 1944 (Box 2B, Folder 7)
- Personal Papers: Publications by Unterberger. Includes National War Labor Board writings, Bureau of Labor Statistics, dissertation, drafts, notes, research files, articles, books. (Box 2C)
  - War Labor Board, 1942-1945 (Box 2C, Folder 1)
  - Ages of Project Employees, 1936 (Box 2C, Folder 2)
  - 'Mayor Dilworth', 1957 (Box 2C, Folder 3)
  - Employment and Relief, 1934 (Box 2C, Folder 4)
  - Sample Studies of Amounts and Duration of Unemployment Compensation Benefits in Pennsylvania, 1938 (Box 2C, Folder 5)
  - History of the Development of the Attitudes of Organized Labor Toward Unemployment Insurance, 1935-1936 (Box 2C, Folder 6)
  - Exhibit D, 1940 (Box 2C, Folder 7)
  - Movements in Sales, Rate of Stock Turnover, 1927-1936 (Box 2C, Folder 8)
    Biound
  - Changes in Labor and Material Costs in Manufacturing Industry, 1919-1933 (Box 2C, Folder 9)
  - Recent Changes in the Economic Relationship Between the United States and Germany, 1924-1933 (Box 2C, Folder 10)
  - Comparison of Benefit Rights under Laws, 1939 (Box 2C, Folder 11)
  - Exhibit H, 1937 (Box 2C, Folder 12)
  - Employment and Relief In The Pittsburgh Industrial Area, 1938 (Box 2C, Folder 13)
  - Some Aspects of the Law of the Internal Affairs of a Trade Union, 1939 (Box 2C, Folder 14)
  - Operating Under the Taft-Hartley Act, 1947-1948 (Box 2C, Folder 15)
  - Operating Under the Taft-Hartley Law, 1947-1948 (Box 2C, Folder 16)
  - Taft-Hartley Act, 1947-1948 (Box 2C, Folder 17)
  - H. Untenburger, 1953 (Box 2C, Folder 18)
  - S.H.U. Monthly Labor Report, 1953 (Box 2C, Folder 19)
- Personal Papers: Publications by Unterberger. Includes National War Labor Board writings, Bureau of Labor Statistics, dissertation, drafts, notes, research files, articles, books. (Box 2D)
  - Res Files, 1978-1979 (Box 2D, Folder 1)
  - The Evolution of Wage Incentive Systems, 1960 (Box 2D, Folder 2)
  - A Report to The Joint Committee on Continuing Professional Education (Box 2D, Folder 3)
  - Industrial Relations, 1978 (Box 2D, Folder 4)
  - Arbitration of Job Evaluation Cases -and- Arbitration of Wage Incentive Cases (Box 2D, Folder 5)
  - Operating Under the Taft-Hartley Act, 1975 (Box 2D, Folder 6)
  - Guaranteed Wage and Supplementary Unemployment Pay Plans (Box 2D, Folder 7)
  - Guaranteed Wage and Supplementary Unemployment Pay Plans (Box 2D, Folder 8)
  - 1, 1943 (Box 2D, Folder 9)
  - 2, 1943 (Box 2D, Folder 10)
  - 3, 1943 (Box 2D, Folder 11)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Airline Pilots Association Case (Box 3)
  - S. Herbert Unterberger - Airline Strike, 1973-1975 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Airline Strikes, 1973-1975 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Trunkline Carriers' Responses to Information Request A-13, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - National Labor Policy, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Trunkline Carriers, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Mutual Aid Pack Investigation - Trunkline Carriers, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Mutual Aid Pact, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - ALPA, 1958-1975 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - ALPA, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Airlines Mutual Aid Pact, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Mutual Aid Pact Investigation, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Airlines Mutual Aid Agreement, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Red, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files; Airline Pilots Association Case (Box 4)
  - Airlines Mutual Aid Agreement, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Mutual Aid Pact Investigation, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board Data, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Handbook of Airline Statistics 1973 Edition (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - ALPA, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Scenario, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Deregulation - General, 1975-1977 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board - Aircraft Operating Cost and Performance Report, 1969-1976 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board - Aircraft Operating Cost and Performance Report, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Airline Pilots Association Case (Box 5)
  - ALPA, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - ALPA, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - ALPA, 1966-1970 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Airline Pilots Association Case (Box 6)
  - ALPA, 1965-1970 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Misc., 1971 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - ALPA - Production, 1960-1980 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Misc. Articles, 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Near Midair Collision Report of 1968, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Preliminary Report of the Special Review Board -and- Relevant Material Presented to the Board by ALPA and United Air Lines, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - FAA Air Traffic Activity - Fiscal Year 1968 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Board
  - Location Identifiers, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - FAA Air Traffic Activity - Calendar Year 1971 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Airline Pilots Association Case (Box 7)
  - Alphabetical and Numeric Flight List for January 1 -thru- January 30, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - ALPA, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Handbook of Airline Statistics Jerold Coffee, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - FAA Statistical Handbook of Aviation 1970 Edition (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Airport Activity Statistics of Certificated Route Air Carriers, 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - FAA Air Traffic Activity Calendar Year 1968, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - United Air Lines, Inc. -and- Air Line Pilots Association, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Age - Wage Analysis ALPA Pilot Membership, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - A Comparative Analysis of the Compensation of Airline Pilots, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Handbook of Airline Statistics 1971 Edition (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Accident Summaries 1964-1973 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Misc., 1972 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Airline Pilots Association Case (Box 8)
  - Airlines Mutual Aids Pact, 1969-1971 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board, 1959-1963 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Airlines Mutual Aid Pact, 1969-1972 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Trunkline Carriers' Responses to Information Request A-12, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Mutual Aid Pact, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Unterberger, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - ALPA Mutual Aid Fact Briefs of Parties to Cabs, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Mutual Aid Pact Investigation, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Airline Strike Insurance (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - 'Master Listing', 1974 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - 'Master Listing' 2, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - 'Master Listing' 3, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - 'Master Listing' 4, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - 'Master Listing' 5, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Airline Pilots Association Case (Box 9)
  - Testimony on Proposed Deregulation of the Airline Industry (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - A Study of Profitable Short-Haul Air Transportation in Dense Markets, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Comment on S.H.&; E. Summary (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - CPUC Load Factor Report Form 1504.42, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - An Analysis of the Interstate Air Carrier Regulatory Forum, Volume 1, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Planning for Growth- PSA is Increasing its Airline Fleet, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - CPUC Decision No.87207: Application of PSA for Ex Parte or Authority to Increase Airfares, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - CPUC Load Factor Report Form 1504.43, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - CPUC Load Factor Report Form 1504.44, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - CPUC PSA Application No.56973 For Increase in Passenger Fares, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - CPUC Form 1511: Interstate Air Passengers Origin and Destination Report, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - CPUC Load Factor Report Form 1504.41, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission Form 10-K, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission Form 10-Q, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission Form 10-Q, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission Form 10-K, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - An Analysis of the Effects of Route Restriction Removal and Discretionary Authority, Volume III, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Report of Financial and Operating Statistics for Certified Air Carriers (Blank) (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Transcript of the 7th Session of the 14th Biennial Convention of the Airline Pilots Association, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - A comparative Analysis of the Compensation of Air Line Pilots, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Statement of Arthur F. Kelly Before the Subcommittee on Aviation in the US Senate, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Air Carrier Financial Statistics, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Air Carrier Traffic Statistics, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Air Carrier Financial Statistics, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Letter to J.J. O'Donnell Regarding "Airline Strike Insurance", 1975 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Letter to J.J. O'Donnell with Report on ALPA Commuter Air Line Study, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Letter to J.J. O'Donnell on United Airlines and the Fuel Crisis, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Letter to Recipients of "Air Carrier Traffic Statistics", 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Age-Wage Analysis: ALPA Pilot Membership 1974, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Opinion and Award Re: Contract Terms and B-737 Crew Complement, ALPA Vs. Aloha, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Opinion and Award Re: Crew Complement on B-737 Aircraft, ALPA vs. Aloha, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Opinion and Award Regarding Crew Size on B-737, United Air Lines vs. ALPA, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Special Review Board Report and Recommendations and Related Requests for Data, United Air Lines Vs. ALPA, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Domestic Fare Structure- CAB, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - The Domestic Route System: Analysis and Policy Recommendations, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - An Analysis of the Effects of Route Restriction Removal and Discretionary Authority, Volume I, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Letter to J.J. O'Donnell on Preliminary Report of Studies on the Proposed Deregulation of the Airline Industry, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - An Analysis of the Effects of Route Restriction Removal and Discretionary Authority, Volume II, Part I (pp.1-283), 1977 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - An Analysis of the Effects of Route Restriction Removal and Discretionary Authority, Volume II, Part II (pp.284-504), 1977 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - An Analysis of US Air Carrier Domestic Route Authority, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - An Analysis of the Intrastate Air Carrier Regulatory Forum, Volume II. Technical Report, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Report to Congress by Comptroller Gen.: Lower Airline Costs per Passenger are Possible in the US and Could Result in Lower Fares, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Proceedings of the Workshop: Air Transportation Demand and Systems Analysis (MIT), 1975 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Oppenheimer & Co. Industry Brief Regarding Structural Changes in the Aircraft Industry, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Letter from Jerry Barker to J.J. O'Donnell on Kennedy/Cannon Bill, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Statement of J.J. O'Donnell Before Committees on Commerce and on Public Works and Transportation Regarding Airline Deregulation Proposals (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - News Clipping: "Eastern Chief Steals Show at Deregulation Hearings", 1977 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Congressional Record: Thursday, February 10th, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Arguments Against Deregulation and Copy of Deregulation Package (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Federal Aviation Act of 1958: S.689, 95th Congress, 1st Session, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Letter to ALPA regarding Necessary Information for ALPA's Effective Dealing with Proposed Airline Industry Deregulation, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Reports on Congressional Hearings from March 21st to April 1st by Jerry Baker and Kelly Ross Sent to J.J. O'Donnell, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Letter to J.J. O'Donnell with Draft of Testimony to be Given in Front of Congress (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Letter to Participants in Studies Regarding Proposed Deregulation of Airline Industry, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 54)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Airline Pilots Association Case (Box 9A)
  - Asbecon, 1979 (Box 9A, Folder 1)
  - American Arbitration Association, 1979 (Box 9A, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Department of Labor, 1979 (Box 9A, Folder 3)
  - ACS, 1979 (Box 9A, Folder 4)
  - ACS, 1978-1979 (Box 9A, Folder 5)
  - AMF, 1979 (Box 9A, Folder 6)
  - Acme-Hamilton, 1979 (Box 9A, Folder 7)
  - A+P, 1977-1979 (Box 9A, Folder 8)
  - Allied Chemical, 1979 (Box 9A, Folder 9)
  - Allied Chemical, 1975 (Box 9A, Folder 10)
  - Allied Chemical, 1979 (Box 9A, Folder 11)
  - Allied Chemical, 1978 (Box 9A, Folder 12)
  - American Can, 1979 (Box 9A, Folder 13)
  - American Insulator, 1978 (Box 9A, Folder 14)
  - Federated Metals, 1978-1979 (Box 9A, Folder 15)
  - American Sugar, 1969-1971 (Box 9A, Folder 16)
  - American Sugar, 1969 (Box 9A, Folder 17)
  - Amstar, 1978 (Box 9A, Folder 18)
  - Amstar, 1975-1976 (Box 9A, Folder 19)
  - ARC, 1979 (Box 9A, Folder 20)
  - Armstrong Cork, 1978-1979 (Box 9A, Folder 21)
  - Armstrong Cork, 1978 (Box 9A, Folder 22)
  - Automation Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 9A, Folder 23)
  - Arrow Shirt, 1978-1979 (Box 9A, Folder 24)
  - Ashland Chemical, 1978-1979 (Box 9A, Folder 25)
  - Ashland, 1978 (Box 9A, Folder 26)
  - Atlus Railroad, 1979 (Box 9A, Folder 27)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Airline Pilots Association Case (Box 9B)
  - Inventory of Airframe and Aircraft Engines and Flight Logs, 1969-1976 (Box 9B, Folder 1)
  - Replacement Commuter Air Carrier Service on Certified Carrier Routes, 1976 (Box 9B, Folder 2)
  - Flight Itineraries from Official Airline Guide, 1977 (Box 9B, Folder 3)
  - CAB Study of Disposition of All Applications for New Trunk Line Authority, 1950-1974 (Box 9B, Folder 4)
  - Flight Suspensions and Deletions, 1970-1976 (Box 9B, Folder 5)
  - Air Service Improvement Act of 1977: HR 8813 (Box 9B, Folder 6)
  - Estimated and Actual Airline Fairs for 110 City-pair Markets in 1973 (Box 9B, Folder 7)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Absecon, City of - Atlas Railroad Construction (Box 10)
  - ALPA, 1966-1968 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Flight Data, 1962-1977 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Flight Data, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Flight Data, 1967-1975 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Flight Data, 1968-1972 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - ALPA, 1970-1974 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Bell Telephone - Burroughs Welcome and Company (Box 11)
  - Bell Tel., 1979 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Bell Tel., 1979 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Bell Tel., 1979 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Bell Tel., 1972 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Bell Tel., 1979 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Bendix, 1968-1973 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Bendix, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Bendix, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - The Bendix Corporation, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Bendix, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Bendix, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Bendix, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Bendix, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Boise Cascade, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Wise Foods, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Borough of West Chester, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Budd Co., 1979 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Budd Co., 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Bucks County, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Building (?) Labor Relations - File, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Bulletin Company, 1976-1978 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Bulletin, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Misc., 1967 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Caloric Corporation - Cumberland Transit (Box 12)
  - Caloric Corporation, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Campbell Soup, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Chase Bag, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Chester County IU Unit., 1979 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Citizens Gas and Utility, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Court of Common Pleas Philadelphia, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - City of Philadelphia, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Claire's Shop-Rule, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Coatesville Area School District, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Columbia Moulding Company, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Community Legal Services, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Coplay Cement, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Compton and Knowles Corporation, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Cumberland, Dauphin, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Commonwealth of Pennsylvania (Box 13)
  - 1970, 1970-1978 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - 1971, 1971-1978 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Dept. of Military Affairs, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, 1976-1978 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Comm. Class, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Comm. 77-1276, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Comm. Of PA, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Comm. 77-4238, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Comm. Of PA, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Comm. AFSCME, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Comm., 1979 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Comm. Of PA, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Comm. Affairs, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Comm. Of Pennsylvania, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Comm. 78-291, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Comm. 78-295, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Comm. 77/2010, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Commonwealth of PA, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Commonwealth of Pennsylvania (Box 14)
  - Comm. 77-1143, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Comm. 76-1584, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Comm. 77-1712, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Comm. Of PA, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Comm. 77-336, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Comm. 77-2134, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Comm. 78-1904, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Comm. 78-2543, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Comm. 78-2877, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Comm. 78-831, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Comm., 1979 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Comm. 76/1202, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Comm. 77-1922, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Central States Publishing, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - 1977 - Collection (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Arbitration and Mediation Case Files: Commonwealth of Pennsylvania (Box 15)
  - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Comm. Lig Bd. 76-2142, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Comm. 77-252, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Comm. -BUR 74-1138, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Comm. 78-1609, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Comm. 78-1431, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Comm. 78-2381, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 11)